DOANH NGUYEN

Bachelor's degree at EASTERN INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY

vandoanh94@gmail.com

Summary

Two years of experience in Information Technology. I had worked a year as a help desk tech. However, I did not find the passion so I became a software developer and it's awesome. I have been a front-end developer for six months and have chance to work with Xamarin platform. My focus is on researching and understanding new technologies, supporting other team members and solving problems in project.

Experience

Web Developer at Orient Software Development Corp.

August 2017 - Present

Technical Proficiencies

- C#, ASP.NET, Core, MVC, Web API
- JavaScript, AngularJS, Bootstrap, Angular 4, HTML & CSS
- WebView Xamarin

IT Helpdesk at VPBank

March 2017 - July 2017 (5 months)

Offer supports and technical assistance to hundreds of VP Bank's officers in five months.

My role and responsibilities were as follows:

- Install, test and configure new workstations, peripheral equipment and software
- Responding to gueries via chat, email, or phone
- Providing technical assistance for questions and problems.
- Remotely accessing hardware or software for clients to make changes and fix problems

Technical Support at FPT Shop (Fptshop.com.vn)

March 2016 - September 2016 (7 months)

My role and responsibilities were as follows:

- Install, Upgrade or Repair Computer, Laptop and Smart Phone.
- Support, Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone, social network and email
- Assist to configure, troubleshoot Computer, Scanner, Printer and Internet Network in Store.
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Partner Company.

IT Helpdesk at Puratos

June 2015 - December 2015 (7 months)

My role and responsibilities were as follows:

- Configure, troubleshoot Computer, Laptop, Scanner, Printer and Internet Network in the Company.
- Support, troubleshoot and answer staff's queries in different agencies vie TeamViewer and IP phone.
- Developing and maintaining corporate information systems.

Education

EASTERN INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY

Bachelor's degree, Information Technology, 2012 - 2017

DOANH NGUYEN

Bachelor's degree at EASTERN INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY

vandoanh94@gmail.com



Contact DOANH on LinkedIn